ALEXANDRU STRAMBEANU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+1 (415) 528 0390 eugenalx@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/alexandru-eugen-strambeanu github.com/eugenalx

Full Stack Developer with five years of experience leading both front-end and back-end development, and performing quality assurance. Led teams of 2-6 people across technology, business and design departments.

SKILLS

PHP/Laravel

JavaScript/React/Vue

HTML5/CSS

Python

MySQL

EDUCATION

International business law

Master's degree Romanian-American University Bucharest 2005 – 2007

Financial management

Master's degree Romanian-American University Bucharest 2003 – 2005

Management and marketing

Bachelor's degree Romanian-American University Bucharest 1999 –2003

CERTIFICATES

PHP

SQL/MySQL

Python

Responsive Web Design

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full-Stack Developer

EAC Sheilding, LA Habra, California

March 2023 - Present

- Implement QR code system for inventory tracking.
- Defined and developed the responsive EAC Shielding platform using HTML5, CSS3, PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/React
- Tested platform across browsers, operating systems, and devices.
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.

Full-Stack Developer

Dotbite, Vienna, Austria June 2022 – December 2022

- Defined and developed the responsive presentation layer using HTML5, CSS3, PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vue.
- Tested websites across browsers, operating systems, and devices.
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.

Web Developer

MaffBags, Bucharest, Romania December 2020 – February 2022

- Developed interactive e-commerce websites using PHP, JavaScript, MySQL, and Liquid.
- Developed and maintained websites using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Worked with clients to gather requirements and develop solutions that meet their needs
- Tested websites across browsers, operating systems, and devices.

Web Developer

Nazmie Edu, Bucharest, Romania July 2017 – November 2020

- Developed interactive web application using PHP/Laravel and MySQL.
- Defined and developed the responsive presentation layer using HTML5, CSS3, PHP/Laravel, JavaScript, and jQuery.
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.

Quality Assurance Manager

Alexander Bake Shop, Bucharest, Romania January 2014 – January 2018

• Oversaw operations of the finance department, set goals and objectives, and designed a framework for these to be met.

Financial Manager

Colts Farm & Food, Bucharest, Romania February 2011 – January 2014

 Supervised and managed all operations of a mid-size retail store with heavy foot traffic.